Past Lives is a drama, romance film directed by Celine Song.
After decades apart, childhood friends Nora and Hae Sung are reunited in New York for one fateful
weekend as they confront notions of destiny, love, and the choices that make a life.
Nora, played by Greta Lee.
Hae Sung, played by Teo Yoo.
Arthur, played by John Magaro.
Young Nora, played by Moon Seung-ah.
Young Hae Sung, played by Yim Seung-min.
Nora's Mom, played by Yoon Ji-hye.
Past Lives is a 2023 romantic drama film written and directed by
Celine Song in her feature directorial debut.
Starring Greta Lee, Teo Yoo, and John Magaro, it follows two childhood friends over the course of 24 years while
they contemplate the nature of their relationship as they grow apart, living different lives.
The plot is semi-autobiographical and inspired by real events from Song's life.
Past Lives premiered at the Sundance Film Festival on January 21, 2023, and was released by A24 in the United States on
June 2 and by CJ ENM in South Korea on a limited release on February 26, 2024, and a wide release on March 6.
The film received critical acclaim and grossed $42.7 million worldwide.
It was named one of the top ten films of 2023 by the National Board of Review and the American Film Institute, receiving multiple accolades, with five nominations at the
81st Golden Globe Awards including for Best Motion Picture - Drama and nominations at the 96th Academy Awards for Best Picture and Best Original Screenplay.
Since its release, it has been included in lists of the
best films of the 2020s and the 21st century.
The film explores themes of new york city, immigrant,
friendship, nostalgia, woman between two men.
The tone is emotional.